<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Xufu Pet Battle Blog</title>
    <description>Read the latest news and updates from wow-petguide.com</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <link>https://www.wow-petguide.com</link>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 12:35:16  GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Shadowlands Prepatch - All you need to know</title>
      <description>The Prepatch is here! And it brought some substantial changes to WoW Pet Battling. Oof size: Large&#13;
&#13;
A very brief overview of the changes:&#13;
&#13;
Black Claw and similar abilities changed in the way they work&#13;
Flock and similar abilities appliying Shattered Defenses have been significantly nerfed&#13;
Twilight Meteorite and other cleave abilities had their damage reduced slightly&#13;
Many healing abilities have been changed to heal flat amounts instead of a variance&#13;
Many, many, abilities have been  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=268</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 10:56:57 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=268</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donation of $1000 made to Panthera.org</title>
      <description>Just after the server move the donation goal over at Ko-Fi was reached and I've just made the payment to my chosen charity: www.panthera.org&#13;
&#13;
After looking at more than 2 dozen charities around tigers and wild cats, Panthera seemed the most fitting and trustworthy. They are fully dedicated to big cats and their entire focus is on their conservation. Their efforts are widespread, from supporting shelters to fighting poachers all the way to influencing legislation in countries where endangered  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=267</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 18:56:20 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=267</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Server-Move September 29th</title>
      <description>Edit on September 29th&#13;
&#13;
Because of a very unfortunate mistake on my end (timezones are difficult sometimes -.-) the server move happened a day early. My apologies for that. &#13;
On top of that, it caused a lot of issues, some small some large. Large meaning something like: not possible to login through Battle.net, error when writing comments, not possible to browse strategies. Issues with which it would be impossible to browse the page. I kept it offline for that reason.&#13;
&#13;
In the meanwhile, I  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=266</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 17:15:13 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=266</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brewfest</title>
      <description>It's time to tap some kegs and bust some heads, because it's Brewfest on Azeroth!&#13;
&#13;
This in-game event lasts just over two weeks, and offers many things for just about any kind of collector: mounts, transmogs, toys, and last but not least pets!&#13;
&#13;
Brewfest offers three pets, all of which can be purchased from a vendor. For Alliance, you'll need to head outside Ironforge to find Belbi Quikswitch, and for Horde it will be outside Orgrimmar with Blix Fixwidget.&#13;
&#13;
The currency you'll need for the  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=265</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 21:06:27 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=265</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inaugural PvP Pet Battle Tournament! (NA Servers)</title>
      <description>Gerissar#1480 is organizing a Pet Battle Tournament with some really cool prizes, but most importantly lots of fun! Read on for more details:&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Test your mettle against other players with your best pet battle skills! Does your team of pets have what it takes to take you to the top?!&#13;
&#13;
Sign up here to find out (https://challonge.com/g8yrzg43)! &#13;
More information can be found on the Tournament Discord (https://discord.gg/QCyzPya).&#13;
</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=264</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 21:29:56 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=264</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jenafur Has Been Found!</title>
      <description>Today, after nearly a year-long search, Jenafur was officially solved!&#13;
&#13;
The person who solved the puzzle is named Paul, and he does not play World of Warcraft himself, but stated he does enjoy solving puzzles. &#13;
&#13;
Hey there, Iâm Paul. Iâm not a WoW player, in fact I donât play many video games at all these days, but I am into puzzle solving. A friend of mine had been telling me off and on all about the difficulties the WoW community has had with this puzzle, and convinced me to take a  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=263</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2020 22:35:18 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=263</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Donation Goal: Helping our Tigers</title>
      <description>Update September 18th&#13;
After just 6 days the goal is reached, wow. I'm speechless. Thank you! I am very grateful for being in such an amazing community.&#13;
Thing is... I haven't had a chance to decide on a charity, yet. So for now I've increased the goal to $400 and will find a fitting charity this weekend! &#13;
That also means, the final amount to be donated will be $1000! &#13;
&#13;
[hr]&#13;
&#13;
Just today we reached our last donation goal over on Ko-Fi (https://ko-fi.com/xufu) which went to our core members,  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=261</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 12:22:03 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=261</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congratulations to the winners!</title>
      <description>Our Shadowlands Giveaway has now concluded and 40 winners have been selected at random. And they are....  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=260</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 21:49:50 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=260</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadowlands Beta Access Giveaway</title>
      <description>Update September 8 - Entry to the giveaway is now closed, thank you for participating!&#13;
The winners will be announced later today :-)&#13;
&#13;
[hr]&#13;
&#13;
Would you like to see the skys above Bastion, explore the beauty of Ardenweald, or give Torghast a try early on? Thanks to Blizzards community team, we have the pleasure of giving away 40 beta accesses!&#13;
&#13;
All you need to do for a chance to get one of them is reply to this news entry and tell us which Shadowlands pet you are looking forward to the  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=259</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 19:19:16 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=259</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadowlands Preparations!</title>
      <description>We've got a release date! October 27th, Shadowlands will arrive. &#13;
The Pre-Patch will likely hit a couple of weeks earlier and it will bring substantial changes (https://wow-petguide.com/?News=249) to pet battling. Xu-Fu's is in the middle of preparing for this upheaval of pet battle strategies, because many of them will not work anymore and will need to be changed or even removed.&#13;
&#13;
To give you the best experience through this process, we are using a phased approach outlined here:&#13;
&#13;
Phase 1  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=257</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 10:36:44 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=257</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cataclysm Timewalking</title>
      <description>We must now go back to a time when the very land itself cries out in agony, as the one meant to watch over the earth and deep places of the world rends our home. Deathwing wrought a terrible change upon Azeroth, and those of the Infinite Dragonflight seek to break the timeline, just as the former Earth-Warder sought to do the same to our kingdoms. This is where you come in, champion. Preserve the timeline, defeat the Infinite Dragonflight, and maybe pick up a few pets along the  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=255</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 06:23:03 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=255</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Guides are up!</title>
      <description>With a big thanks to Nyari for writing them and Shenk for translating, today we have two new guides up on Xu-Fu:&#13;
&#13;
Getting Started on Pet Battling (https://www.wow-petguide.com/index.php?m=GettingStarted) - detailing the best ways to get your first pet to level 25&#13;
Recommended Addons (https://www.wow-petguide.com/index.php?m=RecommendedAddons) - a list and quick explanation of the most widely used pet battle addons&#13;
&#13;
Both are excellent resources and will hopefully help many fresh battlers  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=254</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 21:40:47 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=254</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darkmoon Faire ~~ August 2nd - August 8th</title>
      <description>August's Darkmoon Faire is up, and our main article on how to get all the pets can be found here (https://wow-petguide.com/?News=171).&#13;
&#13;
If you're looking for our Darkmoon Faire strategies for Christoph VonFeasel and Jeremy Feasel, those can be found here (https://www.wow-petguide.com/index.php?m=Darkmoon).&#13;
&#13;
Also, don't forget to pick up your WHEE! buff to get a 10% reputation bonus.&#13;
&#13;
Happy battling!</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=253</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 20:57:14 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=253</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Xu-Fu's is Preparing for the Shadowlands Changes</title>
      <description>Hello, everyone!&#13;
&#13;
As you all know, the Shadowlands Beta is in full swing since getting the character copies this past week. With those copies, beta testers also gained access to some of their roster, which means they can now test the pet battle changes! &#13;
&#13;
Here's what Xu-Fu's staff will be doing in the coming weeks to help soften the blow to how many strats will be effected by said changes:&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Shadowlands Tag&#13;
&#13;
A Shadowlands tag has been added to the site, and will be used in TWO  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=252</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 03:51:22 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=252</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Ready-Check Tables!</title>
      <description>Time for another bigger update here!&#13;
&#13;
Among the most beloved features of Xu-Fu's were the Legion Ready-Checker and the Celestial Tournament Planner. Both sadly had to go away when we added user created strategies and support for breeds.&#13;
Not anymore! Time to bring those features back, and add some things on top :D&#13;
&#13;
Happy to announce the return of Ready-Check Tables!&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
You'll find them on every section of Xu-Fu, including family achievements, dungeons, and - of course - the Celestial  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=250</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 17:09:40 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=250</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadowlands Pet Battle Changes Update from Blizzard</title>
      <description>From Kaivax&#13;
&#13;
Hello pet battlers!&#13;
&#13;
In Shadowlands, there are some core changes to Pet Battles, and while there are many pet battle updates now available for testing, we have quite a bit more coming.&#13;
&#13;
First, we have no plans to make a new pet charm currency this expansion. Polished Pet Charms will remain the standard currency to buy new pets, toys, consumables, and all of the other normally-available vendor purchases.&#13;
&#13;
There are several items that are coming along for testing in this  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=249</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2020 09:32:08 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=249</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battle Pet Compilation for Shadowlands</title>
      <description>With new pets and updates coming out each week, or every other, this is where we'll be compiling that information! &#13;
&#13;
This is in an effort to keep all the pet information in a single place, instead of stretched out across multiple articles, due to the fact that we have a few months, and likely many updates, ahead of us until Shadowlands releases.&#13;
&#13;
With that, let's get to it!&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
There will be NO Currency changes in Shadowlands&#13;
&#13;
First, we have no plans to make a new pet charm currency  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=248</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 01:10:25 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=248</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darkmoon Faire ~~ July 5th - July 11th</title>
      <description>July's Darkmoon Faire is up, and our main article on how to get all the pets can be found here (https://wow-petguide.com/?News=171).&#13;
&#13;
If you're looking for our Darkmoon Faire strategies for Christoph VonFeasel and Jeremy Feasel, those can be found here (https://www.wow-petguide.com/index.php?m=Darkmoon).&#13;
&#13;
Also, don't forget to pick up your WHEE! buff to get a 10% reputation bonus.&#13;
&#13;
Happy battling!</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=247</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2020 06:20:56 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=247</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Pets &amp; Updates from Alpha ~~ 1 July</title>
      <description>Some of these updates are just adding in images of the rares or item the pets drop from, or the vendors they can be purchased from.&#13;
&#13;
However! There are a couple of new pet models, and one pet whose name was changed a little and fleshed out some.&#13;
&#13;
As Always:&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Spoiler warning!&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
~~~~&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Previous Datamined Article Links&#13;
&#13;
24 June 20: Datamined Pets ~~ 24 June (https://wow-petguide.com/index.php?News=243)&#13;
&#13;
18 June 20: New Pets &amp; Abilities  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=246</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 22:42:08 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=246</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer Pet Sale -- Mists of Pandaria CE's Pet Included!</title>
      <description>Blizzard has launched its summer sale, and a select number of pets have been marked at 50% off. &#13;
&#13;
What's exciting, though, is that the Pandaria Collector's Edition pet, Lucky Quilen Cub, is included in this sale!&#13;
&#13;
Pets for Sale&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
[h3]Lucky Quilen Cub[/h3]&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
This charming pet from Pandaria is back!&#13;
&#13;
Although Lucky Quilen Cubs resemble animated statues, their hard-as-stone skin conceals an affectionate heart. These trusted companions will look up to you and faithfully follow your  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=245</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 23:01:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=245</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Timewalking Dungeon Bonus Events</title>
      <description>Blizzard has given us back-to-back Timewalking Bonus weeks, and here are all of our articles on the pets that can be found from the dungeons, raids, and vendors during these events:&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
[h3]Burning Crusade (https://wow-petguide.com/?News=213)[/h3]&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
[h3]Wrath of the Lich King (https://wow-petguide.com/?News=218)[/h3]&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
[h3]Cataclysm (https://wow-petguide.com/?News=222)[/h3]&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
[h3]Mists of Pandaria (https://wow-petguide.com/?News=231)[/h3]&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
The only one that doesn't have any pets  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=244</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 01:38:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=244</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Datamined Pets ~~ 24 June</title>
      <description>We got some new pets!&#13;
&#13;
As always, though: SPOILER WARNING!&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
~~~~~&#13;
&#13;
~~~~&#13;
&#13;
~~~&#13;
&#13;
~~&#13;
&#13;
~&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Previous Datamined Article Links&#13;
&#13;
18 June 20: New Pets &amp; Abilities (https://www.wow-petguide.com/index.php?News=240)&#13;
&#13;
11 June 20: Datamined Pets (https://www.wow-petguide.com/index.php?News=238)&#13;
&#13;
6 June 20: Datamined Pet / Pet NPC Models (https://www.wow-petguide.com/index.php?News=236) (Updated with flavor text &amp; sources!)&#13;
&#13;
12 May 20: Pet Changes  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=243</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 09:07:15 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=243</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jenafur has a New Clue &amp; Uuna got a Hotfix!</title>
      <description>[h3]Jenafur[/h3]&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Today brought us another clue, as Jenafur, one of the longest-running secrets of WoW, is still eluding the Secret Finders among us:&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Finally you'll just need to set the tune, to find the pattern take a top-down zoom&#13;
&#13;
Clue on 16 May 20:&#13;
&#13;
Only one thing gets a kitty into the right mood, when you open up a can of just the right food&#13;
&#13;
Clue on 23 March 20:&#13;
&#13;
kibbles of 4, sets the time, of a 4/4 beat, and defines the lines&#13;
&#13;
Clue on 8 January 20:&#13;
&#13;
Four Kibbles  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=242</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 02:39:56 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=242</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Midsummer Fire Festival &amp; Seasonal Pet</title>
      <description>Things are heating up on Azeroth as summer is finally here. So, let's light some fires and get some pets!&#13;
&#13;
For the Midsummer Fire Festival holiday there there four pets, and today also marks the beginning of summer when the seasonal pet, Qiraji Guardling, becomes available.&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Midsummer Fire Festival&#13;
&#13;
From this holiday, three of the pets are through a vendor, and the fourth is through defeating the holiday boss: Ahune, the Frost Lord. All of these pets are cageable, so if you don't have  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=241</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 18:38:39 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=241</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Pets &amp; Abilities</title>
      <description>We got some new pets &amp; abilities!&#13;
&#13;
As always, though: SPOILER WARNING!&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
~~~~~&#13;
&#13;
~~~~&#13;
&#13;
~~~&#13;
&#13;
~~&#13;
&#13;
~&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Previous Datamined Article Links&#13;
&#13;
11 June 20: Datamined Pets (https://www.wow-petguide.com/index.php?News=238)&#13;
&#13;
6 June 20: Datamined Pet / Pet NPC Models (https://www.wow-petguide.com/index.php?News=236) (Updated with flavor text &amp; sources!)&#13;
&#13;
12 May 20: Pet Changes (https://www.wow-petguide.com/index.php?News=234)&#13;
&#13;
12 April 20: Datamined Potential Pet Models  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=240</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 04:05:49 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=240</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pet Battle Bonus Week &amp; Super Squirt for NA</title>
      <description>The time has come, once again, to level all your pets! &#13;
&#13;
Tuesday brings the pet battle bonus week, and The Sign of the Critter offers a 200% increase on pet experience, so it's the perfect time to tackle that queue. &#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Repeatable Tamers&#13;
&#13;
If you'd like to know what repeatable trainers to look out for this week, head over to our Powerleveling Guide (https://www.wow-petguide.com/index.php?m=Powerleveling) to find out which ones are great for maximizing the use of the bonus xp. It will also  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=239</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 14:44:53 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=239</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Datamined Pets ~~ 11 June 2020</title>
      <description>We got some new pets in this latest build! There's a little flavor text, placeholder abilities, a few locations, but mostly just models.&#13;
&#13;
As always, though: SPOILER WARNING!&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
~~~~~&#13;
&#13;
~~~~&#13;
&#13;
~~~&#13;
&#13;
~~&#13;
&#13;
~&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Previous Datamined Article Links&#13;
&#13;
6 June 20: Datamined Pet / Pet NPC Models (https://www.wow-petguide.com/index.php?News=236) (Updated with flavor text &amp; sources!)&#13;
&#13;
12 May 20: Pet Changes (https://www.wow-petguide.com/index.php?News=234)&#13;
&#13;
12 April 20: Datamined Potential  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=238</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 20:42:20 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=238</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darkmoon Faire ~~ June 7th - 13th</title>
      <description>June's Darkmoon Faire is up, and our main article on how to get all the pets can be found here (https://wow-petguide.com/?News=171).&#13;
&#13;
If you're looking for our Darkmoon Faire strategies for Christoph VonFeasel and Jeremy Feasel, those can be found here (https://www.wow-petguide.com/index.php?m=Darkmoon).&#13;
&#13;
Also, don't forget to pick up your WHEE! buff to get a 10% reputation bonus.&#13;
&#13;
Happy battling!</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=237</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 19:29:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=237</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Datamined Pet / Pet NPC Models</title>
      <description>Hello, there! Seems like it's been a while since we've had a nice pet update from the Alpha, and you'd be correct.&#13;
&#13;
However, we've come across some sneaky models listed under NPC &gt; Battle Pet, instead of just finding them in the Battle Pet section. This could mean they are purely NPC pet models of potential battle pet-type tamers, and/or their pets. However, we might also see these as player pet models at some point, and I'm certainly excited about some of them!&#13;
&#13;
Before we get started,  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=236</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 02:11:07 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=236</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where on Azeroth is Jenafur?</title>
      <description>In one of the longest-running secrets of WoW, Jenafur is still eluding the Secret Finders among us. However, a few days ago there was another clue, Scooby Doos:&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Only one thing gets a kitty into the right mood, when you open up a can of just the right food&#13;
&#13;
Clue on 23 March:&#13;
&#13;
kibbles of 4, sets the time, of a 4/4 beat, and defines the lines&#13;
&#13;
Clue on 8 January 20:&#13;
&#13;
Four Kibbles bounce in time, &#13;
Four Kibbles count the time&#13;
&#13;
Here's a review of everything that's been confirmed so far  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=235</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 07:37:11 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=235</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadowlands Alpha ~~ 5/12/20</title>
      <description>Not much has changed or been added to the Shadowlands Alpha as far as pets are concerned, but we do have a few updates.&#13;
&#13;
Before we get into those, though, we have our obligatory spoiler warning:&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
~~~~~&#13;
&#13;
~~~~&#13;
&#13;
~~~&#13;
&#13;
~~&#13;
&#13;
~&#13;
&#13;
And with that out of the way, off we go!&#13;
&#13;
Previous articles:&#13;
&#13;
Datamined Potential Pet Models (https://wow-petguide.com/?News=225)&#13;
Shadowlands Alpha Pet Information (https://wow-petguide.com/?News=223)&#13;
&#13;
Here's what we'll be going over in this  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=234</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 08:26:41 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=234</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confirmed Bug: Uuna's World Tour</title>
      <description>For anyone looking to complete Uuna's world tour to work on getting their Baa'l pet, you might run into an issue.&#13;
&#13;
Several players in the last few days have run into a bug with Uuna's dialogue not being triggered at the Gate of the Setting Sun, and despite doing an exhaustive number of potential 'fixes', nothing seems to work.&#13;
&#13;
After some run-of-the-mill responses from Blizzard in the ticket system, someone finally received a response to let people know they're aware of the  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=233</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 05:49:55 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=233</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congratulations, J0ker!</title>
      <description>We have a winner!&#13;
&#13;
Congratulations to  for winning the Shadowlands Epic Edition key! A random roll has decided, you can see the ceremonious process in this short video (https://wow-petguide.com/files/5_year_winner_roll.mp4) :D&#13;
&#13;
Thank you so much for all the wonderful wishes and the amazing pictures you all sent in. It's been an amazing week, seeing new ones every day. I'm glad it was a random roll or otherwise I would have had an incredibly hard time picking my favourite!&#13;
&#13;
Meanwhile, our  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=232</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 12:00:06 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=232</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mists of Pandaria Timewalking</title>
      <description>The timeline is once more in danger, and the Bronze Dragonflight has called upon the heroes of Azeroth to venture into the swirling mists of Pandaria. Perhaps we'll also find a few pets hiding amidst the timeways?&#13;
&#13;
This week's timewalking vendor offers two pets: the Paradox Spirit &amp; the Infinite Hatchling, and they both cost 2200 Timewarped Badges.&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
However, there's also an achievement reward pet from Stormstout Brewery: the Hopling. &#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
It's a reward from Ling-Ting's Herbal  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=231</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 05:58:44 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=231</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darkmoon Faire ~~ May 3rd - 9th</title>
      <description>May's Darkmoon Faire is up, and our main article on how to get all the pets can be found here (https://wow-petguide.com/?News=171).&#13;
&#13;
If you're looking for our Darkmoon Faire strategies for Christoph VonFeasel and Jeremy Feasel, those can be found here (https://www.wow-petguide.com/index.php?m=Darkmoon).&#13;
&#13;
Also, don't forget to pick up your WHEE! buff to get a 10% reputation bonus.&#13;
&#13;
Happy battling!</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=230</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 10:41:38 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=230</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy Birthday!</title>
      <description>&#13;
=== The giveaway is concluded and you can find out about the lucky winner here (https://www.wow-petguide.com/?News=232) ===&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
It's been five years already!&#13;
So much has changed around here in that time and what started as a little page with a mere 21 strategies is now the central hub for WoW pet battling strategies, hosting over 5000 strategies, with almost 15k registered users. Couldn't be more proud, thank you for making this an amazing community :-)&#13;
&#13;
To celebrate, I have a special  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=228</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 10:15:05 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=228</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Children's Week</title>
      <description>Youâre not quite sure how you got roped into this, but through the haze of last nightâs drinking of a particularly heady Pandaren brew, you recall a card game. In fact, as the bits and pieces slowly fall into place while you eat your breakfast, you remember someone unexpected and out of place at the card table: a matronly woman. After being thoroughly trounced, you pushed the winnings toward her. &#13;
&#13;
She smiled, and took only half. âYouâll need the rest for tomorrow,â she said, and  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=229</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 08:46:54 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=229</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pet Battle Bonus Week &amp; Super Squirt for US</title>
      <description>The time has come, once again, to level all your pets! &#13;
&#13;
Tuesday brings the pet battle bonus week, and The Sign of the Critter offers a 200% increase on pet experience, so it's the perfect time to tackle that queue. &#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Repeatable Tamers&#13;
&#13;
If you'd like to know what repeatable trainers to look out for this week, head over to our Powerleveling Guide (https://www.wow-petguide.com/index.php?m=Powerleveling) to find out which ones are great for maximizing the use of the bonus xp. It will also  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=227</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 03:33:48 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=227</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noblegarden</title>
      <description>"A tisket, a tasket, a green and yellow basket..."&#13;
&#13;
A little girl skips by you, dressed in her finest spring garb, singing the familiar rhyme. Her wicker basket is full of brightly colored eggs and it swings in time with the words, as her mother hurries to catch up.&#13;
&#13;
As you walk the path, heading back to where your journey began, the signs of spring are all around you: flowers blooming, earth being made ready for sowing, and the warmth of the sun before it becomes scorching summer heat. It  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=226</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 23:13:54 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=226</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Datamined Potential Pet Models</title>
      <description>We're back, and with some potential pet models we might be seeing in the next expansion!&#13;
&#13;
The models below were chosen based on three factors:&#13;
&#13;
1. They're similar to a model that has come up in the alpha pet filters (Foxes)&#13;
&#13;
2. They're similar or re-skins of models found in the live version of the game.&#13;
&#13;
3. Candidates for potential new models that looked way too cool to leave off the list.&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
All of the images below were found on Wowhead at this link here  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=225</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 22:21:49 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=225</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compare your collection</title>
      <description>Quick news in between the Shadowland announcements, I just finished a new tool!&#13;
The Collection Comparator (https://www.wow-petguide.com/index.php?m=Compare)&#13;
&#13;
It does what it says, simple as that!&#13;
Easily compare the collections of any two characters (or users) and filter for whatever you like to see. Special note to the "Quick Filters"!&#13;
&#13;
Enjoy, have fun, stay safe and let me know if you like it!</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=224</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 17:06:21 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=224</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadowlands Alpha Pet Information ~~ 9 April 20</title>
      <description>It's official--the first wave of the Shadowlands Alpha keys have gone out, and Wowhead has datamined a whole load of new information for players in all walks of the game, including battle pets!&#13;
&#13;
Before we get into any of this, we'll put this up for anyone who doesn't want to see these changes before Shadowlands releases:&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
~~~~~&#13;
~~~~&#13;
~~~&#13;
~~&#13;
~&#13;
&#13;
There, now that we've gotten that out of the way, we can take a look at some of the changes that have come up on the alpha.&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Ability  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=223</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 05:19:20 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=223</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cataclysm Timewalking</title>
      <description>We must now go back to a time when the very land itself cries out in agony, as the one meant to watch over the earth and deep places of the world rends our home. Deathwing wrought a terrible change upon Azeroth, and those of the Infinite Dragonflight seek to break the timeline, just as the former Earth-Warder sought to do the same to our kingdoms. This is where you come in, champion. Preserve the timeline, defeat the Infinite Dragonflight, and maybe pick up a few pets along the  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=222</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 06:45:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=222</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darkmoon Faire ~~ April 5th - 11th</title>
      <description>April's Darkmoon Faire is up, and our main article on how to get all the pets can be found here (https://wow-petguide.com/?News=171).&#13;
&#13;
If you're looking for our Darkmoon Faire strategies for Christoph VonFeasel and Jeremy Feasel, those can be found here (https://www.wow-petguide.com/index.php?m=Darkmoon).&#13;
&#13;
Also, don't forget to pick up your WHEE! buff to get a 10% reputation bonus.&#13;
&#13;
Happy battling!</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=221</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 18:59:45 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=221</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where on Azeroth is Jenafur?</title>
      <description>In one of the longest-running secrets of WoW, Jenafur is still eluding the Secret Finders among us. However, yesterday there was another clue, Scooby Doos:&#13;
&#13;
kibbles of 4, sets the time, of a 4/4 beat, and defines the lines&#13;
&#13;
I can say I have no idea what any of that means, but it's my sincere hope that it inspires someone on the Discord.&#13;
&#13;
It joins this clue given on 8 January 20:&#13;
&#13;
Four Kibbles bounce in time, &#13;
Four Kibbles count the time&#13;
&#13;
Here's a review of everything that's been  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=219</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 06:26:39 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=219</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wrath of the Lich King Timewalking</title>
      <description>A chill creeps through the timestream, and the howling of the undead scourge echos through the Caverns of Time. The Bronze dragons have once again called upon the heroes of Azeroth to battle the Infinite Dragonflight, and help preserve the timeline. This time we're being sent to Northrend, to battle the forces and allies of the Lich King. Though there aren't any pets to be found from the WotLK Timewalking dungeons, or the Timewalking Vendor -- Auzin -- there are some pets that can drop during  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=218</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 02:45:47 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=218</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pet Battle Bonus Week &amp; Super Squirt on EU</title>
      <description>The time has come, once again, to level all those new pets that have (hopefully!) dropped for you from the latest patch! Or perhaps there are a few you still need to level to beat the new WQs and pet dungeon?&#13;
&#13;
Never fear; it's pet battle bonus week! The Sign of the Critter offers a 200% increase on pet experience, and it's the perfect time to tackle that queue. &#13;
&#13;
If you'd like to know what repeatable trainers to look out for this week, head over to our Powerleveling Guide  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=217</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 23:33:44 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=217</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Home-Widget: Video Highlights</title>
      <description>A wild widget appears!&#13;
&#13;
 brought up the idea to highlight pet related videos from and for the community, and here they are! &#13;
Conveniently in a little widget on the side for you to push it around to wherever you want it's home to be :D&#13;
It's super fresh so we're still experimenting a little but so far it looks neat.&#13;
&#13;
Are you making videos about pet battles yourself and want to be featured? Cool! &#13;
To keep things under control, we added a few very simple guidelines so go have a read through  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=216</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 18:44:22 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=216</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darkmoon Faire ~~ March 1st - 7th</title>
      <description>March's Darkmoon Faire is up, and our main article on how to get all the pets can be found here (https://wow-petguide.com/?News=171).&#13;
&#13;
Also, don't forget to pick up your WHEE! buff to get a 10% rep bonus for those new 8.3 reputations.&#13;
&#13;
Happy battling!</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=215</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 05:42:43 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=215</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burning Crusade Timewalking</title>
      <description>The Bronze Dragonflight is once again calling on the heroes of Azeroth to help repair the timestreams, and prevent catastrophic changes from happening. Of course, that doesnât mean we canât collect a few pets along the way!&#13;
&#13;
It may not seem obvious at a glance, but the Burning Crusade timewalking vendor does sell pets, or rather the chance for pets to drop. When you visit Cupri in the middle of Shattrath on the second floor of the Terrace of Light, youâll see she has Bag of Fishing  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=213</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 20:15:48 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=213</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frontpage Update</title>
      <description>A little update made it to the frontpage right now with a couple of changes and new additions:&#13;
&#13;
No more split between "small" and "large" news. There are just news. Right here in this column.&#13;
The side panels or menu items can be rearranged to your liking now! Only if you are logged in though. Just use the little arrows and push the ones you use the most often to the top :-)&#13;
A few new side panels appeared! Among them a leaderboard showing the Xu-Fu users with the top 25 collections for each  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=212</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 16:51:27 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=212</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Love is in the Air</title>
      <description>You walk into the capital then stop dead in your tracks. Hearts of pink, red, and white litter every possible surface of the buildings, and a not so subtle aroma clings to the air with a persistence that leaves you lightheaded. Coy glances and breathy laughter follow you through the city as you go about your errands, while you try not to think too hard about what force in nature decided it was a good idea to give a goblin wings, and the power to bestow love on unsuspecting passerby. Business  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=211</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2020 12:11:43 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=211</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darkmoon Faire ~~ 2 February - 8 February</title>
      <description>February's Darkmoon Faire is up, and our main article on how to get all the pets can be found here (https://wow-petguide.com/?News=171).&#13;
&#13;
Also, don't forget to pick up your WHEE! buff to get a 10% rep bonus for those new 8.3 reputations.&#13;
&#13;
Happy battling!</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=210</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 13:54:10 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=210</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8.3 Celebration Giveaway!</title>
      <description>To celebrate 8.3, we are hosting a giveaway! &#13;
&#13;
Up for grabs are these EU codes: &#13;
&#13;
1x Shadowlands Heroic Edition&#13;
1x Whomper &#13;
1x Argi&#13;
1x Brightpaw&#13;
1x Dottie&#13;
&#13;
The giveaway will work through Twitter this time. Here's what you'll need to do:&#13;
&#13;
1. Head over to Twitter and follow @XuFusPetguide (https://twitter.com/XuFusPetguide)&#13;
2. Do the same with @Warcraft (https://twitter.com/Warcraft) (requirement, they sponsored the codes!)&#13;
3. Respond to this tweet  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=209</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 15:01:52 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=209</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lunar Festival </title>
      <description>Fireworks burst in a variety of colors across Moonglade's sky in celebration of the Burning Legion's defeat thousands of years ago. Having thwarted the same enemy on the Broken Shore and Argus, the holiday has taken on a deeper meaner for you than in years past. As you travel across Azeroth, honoring your elders and gaining their favor and wisdom, a sense of peace suffuses your being. Though you may face many trials and tribulations on the road ahead, this is a time of happiness and unity. Of  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=208</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 04:38:03 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=208</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Changes to the BRD Pet Dungeon</title>
      <description>During maintenance on Tuesday, Blizzard pushed some changes to the BRD pet dungeon to Therin Skysong, Alran Heartshade, &amp; Zuna Skullcrush. This should help to further stabilize strategies, and reduce RNG. Since changes have been made, we'd advice any strategy creators for the dungeon to test their strats to see how the changes have impacted said strategies. &#13;
&#13;
Changes&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Therin Skysong&#13;
&#13;
Logic&#13;
Power reduced from 355 to 311&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Math&#13;
Power reduced from 350 to 289&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Alran  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=204</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 10:57:34 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=204</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pet Battle Bonus Week &amp; Super Squirt on EU</title>
      <description>What better way to celebrate a new patch than by leveling all those lovely new friends added to your roster? Or perhaps there are a few you still need to level to beat the new WQs and pet dungeon?&#13;
&#13;
Never fear; it's pet battle bonus week! The Sign of the Critter offers a 200% increase on pet experience, and it's the perfect time to tackle that queue. &#13;
&#13;
If you'd like to know what repeatable trainers to look out for this week, head over to our Powerleveling Guide  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=203</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 22:41:11 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=203</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8.3 PvP Updates</title>
      <description>With the release of patch 8.3 there have been more additions to the PvP pet roster than just new pets. A new weather effect came with the patch and two old ones have been changed. Because of that development we made a revision to the tier lists (meta and families).&#13;
&#13;
Toxic Fumes&#13;
is the newest weather. It has two effects; it extends the duration of any damage over time effect by 1 round (the opposite of cleansing rain) and all pets are considered poisoned. This makes it a versatile ability  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=202</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 16:44:30 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=202</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch 8.3 Pet Information</title>
      <description>On Tuesday, 14 January, Blizzard will release patch 8.3, Visions of N'Zoth. For the pet battlers and collectors in the community, there's a few things to look out for, and forward to! In this patch, we'll be getting:&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
8 new pet battle world quests in Uldum &amp; the Vale of Eternal Blossoms&#13;
&#13;
A new pet battle dungeon: Blackrock Depths&#13;
&#13;
A pet, toy, &amp; mount connected to a month-long quest chain&#13;
&#13;
33 new pets&#13;
&#13;
One new pet toy&#13;
&#13;
Pet Tamer &amp; Battle Relocation: Obalis, Aki the Chosen, &amp;  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=194</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 07:45:14 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=194</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darkmoon Faire ~~ 5 Jan. - 11 Jan.</title>
      <description>January's Darkmoon Faire is up, and our main article for how to get all the pets can be found here (https://wow-petguide.com/?News=171).&#13;
&#13;
As a friendly reminder, today and tomorrow are the last full days to take advantage of the two reputation &amp; experience buffs: WoW's 15th Anniversary gives 15%, and the WHEE! buff from the Darkmoon Faire gives 10%&#13;
&#13;
Happy battling!</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=193</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 22:51:04 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=193</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mists of Pandaria Timewalking</title>
      <description>The timeline is once more in danger, and the Bronze Dragonflight has called upon the heroes of Azeroth to venture into the swirling mists of Pandaria. Perhaps we'll also find a few pets hiding amidst the timeways?&#13;
&#13;
This week's timewalking vendor offers two pets: the Paradox Spirit &amp; the Infinite Hatchling, and they both cost 2200 Timewarped Badges.&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
However, there's also an achievement reward pet from Stormstout Brewery: the Hopling. &#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
It's a reward from Ling-Ting's Herbal  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=192</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 21:32:51 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=192</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy Holidays!</title>
      <description>The end of the year is closing in and for many of you out there, these last days of 2019 will be full of festivities and celebration. I would like to join in by wishing you all the best for those days. May they be filled with joy, happiness and wonderful company for you to find peace and stay in the moment, for there will be many good ones to still experience in this year and decade.&#13;
&#13;
Best seasonal wishes from  and the entire Xu-Fu team!</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=191</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 17:23:39 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=191</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holiday Pet Sale &amp; The Cat Pack</title>
      <description>Happy Holidays, Pet Community! It's the most wonderful time of the year for purchasing Blizzard store pets, and to sweeten the deal, Blizzard has also offered the Cat Pack (https://news.blizzard.com/en-us/world-of-warcraft/23237903/save-big-on-pets-mounts-and-more-during-our-holiday-sale):&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
This time-limited* pawsh bundle contains a feisty litter of Azerothâs furriest (and ficklest) felines. Treat yourself to Azerothâs purriest creaturesâthree mounts and four petsâat a discount! If  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=190</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 05:10:06 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=190</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seasonal Pet: Snowy Owl</title>
      <description>The 21st of December marks the first day of winter, and that means the Snowy Owl will finally spawn in Winterspring!&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
This pet is a requirement to complete Kalimdor Safari, so if you're missing this one, head on over and catch that pet.&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Best of luck to you all, and Happy Battling!</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=189</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2019 04:37:10 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=189</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feast of Winter Veil</title>
      <description>The days are shorter since leaving midsummer behind, and the cold weather has driven all but the most resilientâor fur-coveredâindoors. Fires crackle merrily in their hearths, and the children of Azeroth are counting the minutes until Great Father Winter leaves presents beneath the tree. &#13;
&#13;
While in the capital doing some last-minute shopping, laughter and cheering catches your attention. You turn to find a cadre of people hauling in the giant Winter Veil tree, as children skip and run  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=188</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 08:06:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=188</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auto-Updating Collections</title>
      <description>What's that, no more outdated collections...?&#13;
&#13;
Yep! As part of the updates I'm doing, I've now also added a function that keeps your collection up to date. As long as the character details that are saved with your collection (https://www.wow-petguide.com/?page=collection) are correct, Xu-Fu now updates your collection every 48h.&#13;
 &#13;
So as long as you're not going on a crazy pet shopping spree, you should have a smooth experience browsing strategies here :-) And even if, you can still manually  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=187</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 11:10:01 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=187</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Armory Connection</title>
      <description>A long maintenance just concluded that was necessary to move the page from an old to a newer database connection. This change was required by Blizzard. If you want to know all the details, you can read the full announcement (https://us.forums.blizzard.com/en/blizzard/t/world-of-warcraft-community-api-migration/767).&#13;
&#13;
So what has changed? Not much, sadly. Xu-Fu is a bit more future proof and things won't break suddenly, but there are no new features now. Things might load a little bit faster  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=186</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 13:39:55 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=186</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadowbarb Hatchling: Do You Want to Hatch a Void Bug?</title>
      <description>Just when we thought Blizzard was done adding new pets to the PTR, the latest build has brought a new surprise: meet the Shadowbarb Hatchling!&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
This pet is a reward as part of a quest chain, combined with hatching it through a progression of daily quests. These dailies and quests are attached to the Assaults, needing specific ones to be up depending on where you are in the chain. The dailies will reward 300 xp, and the unique quests will give 900 xp. &#13;
&#13;
Anywho, let's get started on  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=185</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 22:45:53 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=185</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dottie is Now Available for Purchase!</title>
      <description>The 2019 Blizzard charity pet, Dottie, is now available for purchase!&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
We first got to see Dottie at Blizzcon, where the Game Director for Blizzard, Ion Hazzikistas, announced that she would be our 2019 charity pet!&#13;
&#13;
100% of the proceeds will be going to two different charities this year: the Make-A-Wish Foundation (https://wish.org/) and WE.org (https://www.we.org/en-CA/about-we/we-charity/). The links will send you to the charity pages, if you're interested in seeing what your  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=184</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 18:53:47 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=184</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pet Battle Bonus Week &amp; Super Squirt for NA/US!</title>
      <description>It's that time again, pet battlers! The Sign of the Critter is up, and if you're looking to tackle your leveling queue this is the week to do it. &#13;
&#13;
Pet Battle Week brings a 200% bonus to pet experience, which means you can go from 1-25 in no time, depending on the fights. &#13;
&#13;
If you're looking to maximize your leveling with repeatable trainers, take a look at our Powerleveling Guide (https://www.wow-petguide.com/index.php?m=Powerleveling). &#13;
&#13;
As always, though, feel free to peruse the  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=183</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 18:19:49 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=183</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darkmoon Faire  1 Dec 19 - 7 Dec 19</title>
      <description>The Darkmoon Faire is here again! &#13;
&#13;
This particular Darkmoon Faire brings with it the special opportunity for reputation gains.&#13;
&#13;
Sunday: 15th Anniversary Buff (15%) + Pilgrim's Bounty Spirit of Sharing (10%) + Darkmoon Faire Whee! (10%) = 35%&#13;
&#13;
Monday - Saturday: 15th Anniversary Buff (15%) + Darkmoon Faire Whee! (10%) = 25%&#13;
&#13;
So, if you have anything to turn in today, or have some old reputations to grind through dungeons, today would be the day!&#13;
&#13;
As far as pets go, here's our main  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=182</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 09:47:55 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=182</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pilgrim's Bounty</title>
      <description>Tables groan beneath the weight of a variety of dishes, and boisterous conversation fills the air over many a tankard of drink. Stories of glory and thanks are traded like precious gold, as friends new and old take their seats. Every cook and kitchen within the capital cities tirelessly churn out platter upon platter of food, as the citizens of Azeroth make the pilgrimage from far and wide to celebrate the week of Pilgrimâs Bounty. &#13;
&#13;
Just as you lean forward to take the first bite of your  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=181</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 05:31:09 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=181</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8.3 PTR Pet Updates: 21 Nov. 19</title>
      <description>Itâs been quite a turbulent week for pet battlers, as news from Kaivax, Community Manager on the forums, told us there were going to be some big changes coming for us (https://www.wow-petguide.com/?News=179)! Though itâs debatable on whether players are seeing these changes as good, or not, it was encouraging to see some attention being paid to the pet battle system. In a continuation of this, the new PTR build that went live today brought: &#13;
&#13;
A look at the new charity pet&#13;
Changes to the  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=180</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 08:54:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=180</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Changes Coming to Pet Battles</title>
      <description>Earlier, there was a blue post on the Visions of N'Zoth &amp; Pet Battle forums regarding some changes we'll be seeing in 8.3 and beyond.&#13;
&#13;
~~Links to the original posts no longer work~~&#13;
&#13;
From Kaivax:&#13;
&#13;
Hello pet battlers!&#13;
&#13;
Weâve seen some discussion around pet battle changes coming in Visions of NâZoth, and weâd like to discuss those, as well as changes we currently have planned for a future content update.&#13;
&#13;
The Weather Outside is Fight-ful&#13;
&#13;
Weather effects have always been  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=179</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2019 02:17:18 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=179</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Updated Pet Collection Viewer</title>
      <description>I just updated the Pet Collection Viewer (https://www.wow-petguide.com/index.php?m=Collection) because Blizzard made changes to their armory connection that I and many other pages are using. There will be many more updates necessary to keep everything in working condition and ideally you should not notice any changes, perhaps even an improvement here or there :-)&#13;
&#13;
This initial change has a few effects:&#13;
The collection viewer now imports all new pets as well, like Lil' Nefarian or the Anima  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=178</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 14:01:26 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=178</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Pet Battle WQs in 8.3!</title>
      <description>It seems as though a new pet dungeon isn't all we'll be getting in 8.3--we'll be getting some new WQs in the corrupted zones, too!&#13;
&#13;
There's four different battles per zone, against single enemy pets, who are Legendary quality with the Elite Buff, (Reduces Damage by 50%).&#13;
&#13;
The new WQs have been added in the BFA &gt; BfA World Quests tab on the site! &#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Uldum&#13;
&#13;
Dune Buggy&#13;
Defeat the Aqir Sandcrawler&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
This WQ can be found to the right of the Temple of Uldum, at coordinates 35.50,  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=177</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 06:04:39 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=177</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Blackrock Depths Pet Dungeon!</title>
      <description>You've battled your way through multiple pet dungeons, against a wide variety of foes, and you've been victorious. However, in the beginning of your journey you couldn't help but notice there was something not quite right with the enemy pets, as though they'd somehow been changed. Then, your suspicions were confirmed in Gnomeregan, as you encountered sinister figures cloaked in shadows. Now you've cornered them in Blackrock Depths, and you'll finally get to see what these fiendish villains have  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=175</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2019 05:33:30 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=175</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8.3 PTR Pet Updates: 8 Nov. 19</title>
      <description>Yesterday, the PTR was taken down for a wipe, as well as a new build. And guess what? We finally have access to the new pet dungeon: Blackrock Depths! There were also updates to pets weâd previously seen, as well as some new ones joining the pet journal. &#13;
&#13;
In this post, weâll be showing you all the pet updates, and once weâve made it through the pet dungeon, that will be its own post. Let me tell you: the new dungeon is a doozy. &#13;
&#13;
If youâd like to see what all the old pets look  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=174</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 09:16:44 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=174</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World of Warcraft 15th Anniversary</title>
      <description>Happy Birthday, World of Warcraft!&#13;
&#13;
This year, WoW celebrates its 15th anniversary with an event that runs from: &#13;
&#13;
November 5, 2019 â January 7, 2020 (The Americas)&#13;
November 6, 2019 â January 8, 2020 (Europe)&#13;
November 7, 2019 â January 9, 2020 (Asia)&#13;
&#13;
There are a fair few goodies on the horizon for us, including three new mounts: Obsidian Warbreaker, Frostwolf Snarler, and the Stormpike Battle Ram. &#13;
&#13;
The Obsidian Warbreaker's model was inspired by Deathwing, and will require  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=173</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 06:21:38 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=173</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadowland's Pre-Order &amp; Charity Pets</title>
      <description>Another Blizzcon has come and gone, and a great many exciting announcements have been made. For the pet community, this included two new pets: the Anima Wyrmling &amp; Dottie!&#13;
&#13;
Anima Wyrmling&#13;
&#13;
The Anima Wyrmling is the pet players will receive as part of the World of Warcraft: Shadowlands pre-order in the 'Epic Edition', or the highest tier of pre-order. &#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Family: Dragonkin&#13;
Health: 1424&#13;
Speed: 273&#13;
Power: 301&#13;
&#13;
Abilities:&#13;
&#13;
Slot 1: Siphon Life / Gale Slash &#13;
Slot 2: Amplify Magic /  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=172</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 05:21:13 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=172</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Day of the Dead - Nov. 1st - 2nd</title>
      <description>The scent of marigold hangs heavy in the cool air, while laughter, music, and weeping intermingle amidst the headstones. You place the sturdy, white candle on top of the newly carved gravestone in front of you, then light the wick. The flame stutters to life, and then stills, unwavering. The aroma of freshly baked bread makes your mouth water, as you pull the skull-shaped loaf from your pack, and then place it gingerly next to the candle. &#13;
&#13;
Now you wait. &#13;
&#13;
Itâs not long before a familiar,  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=169</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 03:53:39 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=169</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darkmoon Faire Pets</title>
      <description>Carnival music drifts through the air, while children run around, shrieking with glee. Flashes of juggled torchlight illuminate the dirt path in front of the tents, while barkers call to passerby, enticing them to play their games. Above it all, the glowing, orange eye watches onâ¦Always.&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
âCome one, come all! &#13;
&#13;
The Darkmoon Faire is finally here, and you wonât want to miss this, my dears. We have, among our wondrous delights, pets for you that have some bite. There are some that  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=171</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2019 04:53:17 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=171</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where on Azeroth is Jenafur?</title>
      <description>With the Master away, Moroes will play, but who has he invited to Karazhan this time?&#13;
&#13;
Super, the owner of the Secret Finder's discord, released this announcement earlier in regards to Jenafur:&#13;
&#13;
"Hey everyone,&#13;
&#13;
The following clarifications surrounding the Jenafur secret have been confirmed to the staff team:&#13;
&#13;
- The secret is working as intended, is solvable and does not require a group (confirmed for the current step).&#13;
&#13;
- The first step was to talk to Amara. The second step was the  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=168</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 23:48:44 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=168</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet Rikki -- The New RaF Pet!</title>
      <description>On Tuesday, Blizzard implemented a revamp of their Recruit A Friend system (https://news.blizzard.com/en-us/world-of-warcraft/23127426/recruit-a-friend-is-now-live), which will now be accessible from your social tab. Along with showing you who you've recruited, it also tracks all the rewards available from the program. For pet collectors out there, it's time to dust off your friend's list and send out a link, because Blizzard has brought us an adorable new companion. &#13;
&#13;
Meet Rikki!&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
His  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=166</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 06:36:49 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=166</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small 8.3 Pet Update</title>
      <description>The PTR welcomed another build today with an update, though sadly thereâs still no BRD Pet Dungeon in sight, or its rewards. &#13;
&#13;
However!&#13;
&#13;
We did get to see some fleshing out of a few pets coming in 8.3.&#13;
&#13;
Raid&#13;
&#13;
All of the raid pets officially have the bosses theyâll drop from in the Nyâalotha raid!&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Aqir Hivespawn &#13;
This pet will drop from Tekâris, which is a boss in the fifth encounter and part of The Hivemind along with Kaâzir. &#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Eye of Corruption&#13;
This lovely floating  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=165</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 05:12:25 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=165</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burning Crusade Timewalking</title>
      <description>The Bronze Dragonflight is once again calling on the heroes of Azeroth to help repair the timestreams, and prevent catastrophic changes from happening. Of course, that doesnât mean we canât collect a few pets along the way!&#13;
&#13;
It may not seem obvious at a glance, but the Burning Crusade timewalking vendor does sell pets, or rather the chance for pets to drop. When you visit Cupri in the middle of Shattrath on the second floor of the Terrace of Light, youâll see she has Bag of Fishing  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=163</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 15:56:35 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=163</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oct 21 -- Super Squirt Day for US/NA! </title>
      <description>Today is one of those magical days where we get to see the combination of the Pet Battle Bonus Event and the Squirt menagerie fight. So, head on out to those garrisons and get to leveling your pets!&#13;
&#13;
Here's the link to our Squirt strat page (https://www.wow-petguide.com/index.php?Strategy=730), where there are plenty of strategies for you to choose from. Or perhaps you want to try your hand at making one yourself? Go crazy, have fun, and put a dent in that leveling queue!</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=161</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 17:54:50 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=161</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hallow's End Pet Guide</title>
      <description>Itâs that time of year again! Pumpkins are glowing, fingers are sticky from candy, and the Headless Horseman is setting everything on fire. Hallowâs End went live today, and with it comes the opportunity for all those wonderful holiday pets. Though we havenât gotten any new ones to add to our roster this year, this is the perfect opportunity to farm for the ones you might be missing, or perhaps to sell on the auction house. &#13;
&#13;
Hallowâs End boasts a whopping 9 pets that come from a  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=160</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 21:25:12 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=160</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8.3 PTR Update ~~ 16 October 2019</title>
      <description>Those who tried to log in to the PTR today found the servers down, which could only mean one thing: more content! Along with a scad of datamined class changes, auction house tweaks, boss model updates, and much more, we were greeted by some new pets. Iâm happy to report that we will be awash in void, tentacles, and eyeballs, with some lovely new models and abilities! &#13;
&#13;
This content update fleshed out some drops weâll see in three different areas: Corrupted Zones, Horrific Visions, and the  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=158</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 07:26:53 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=158</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Landing Page</title>
      <description>Long in the works, a brand new landing page makes it to Xu-Fu. Exactly the one you are reading on right now :-)&#13;
&#13;
It brings a few new things: a fresh design, a lot more readability thanks to better formatting options, and the biggest change,  is adding News about the Pet Battling world from now on! &#13;
Even more reason to stop by regularly :-)</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=155</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 17:43:05 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=155</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch 8.3 PTR &amp; Conclusion to the Shadowy Figures?</title>
      <description>On October 7th, Blizzard announced patch 8.3, the latest content update to Battle for Azeroth. Not only will we be battling an Old God, but weâll also find out what those Shadowy Figures lurking in our pet dungeons have been up to!&#13;
&#13;
New Pet Dungeon!&#13;
&#13;
When players logged into the PTR on the 7th, we were greeted with two new pet battle achievements:&#13;
&#13;
Pet Battle Challenge: Blackrock Depths&#13;
&#13;
Shadow Stopper â A meta achievement for the completion of the challenge version of five pet  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=153</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 07:02:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=153</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strategy Creation Rules</title>
      <description>The possibility for all registered users to upload their own strategies was extremely successful. Since then, Xu-Fu has grown immensely thanks to everyone who contributes. On a much smaller scale, however, we saw a number of strategies that were not up to the standards we set out. When I created Xu-Fu's Pet Guides, my goal was simply to provide my own strategies. That later turned into providing the best strategies for each fight and a good variety for all different levels of battlers.&#13;
We  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=146</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 12:10:54 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=146</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the team, DragonsAfterDark!</title>
      <description>I have some great news to share, and no, it's not WoW Classic related, sorry. It is, however, related to someone you have stumbled upon almost guaranteed if you've been using Xu-Fu to look up strategies in the last few months. So pretty much everyone who will read this. I am talking about !&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
She is one of the most active pet battlers here on the page and so far has uploaded more than 700 strategies, many of which are the top picks and most favourited for their specific fight.&#13;
If you want  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=145</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 19:59:01 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=145</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linkable comments</title>
      <description>A tiny little update, as requested by , from now on all comments will have a little link-symbol next to them. With this icon, you can copy a direct link to the comment into your clipboard and paste it somewhere else :-)</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=144</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 11:41:25 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=144</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch 8.2 and Pet Update Issues</title>
      <description>The patch is live and with it the usual suspects - API problems ^^&#13;
&#13;
Importing or updating your pet collection from the armory currently returns zero pets. This is an issue on Blizzards side and we'll need to wait until it's been addressed.&#13;
In the meanwhile, it's the perfect opportunity to build some better error messages in so you know what's going on when trying to update your collection :-)</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=143</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 11:59:20 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=143</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Guides!</title>
      <description>In the last weeks, Xu-Fu got a lot of additional help, both from veteran Xu-Fu collaborators and new people. Most of the work has been put into guides and they are definitely worth a shout-out here. &#13;
One by one, the page now hosts:&#13;
&#13;
Pet Powerleveling Guide (https://www.wow-petguide.com/index.php?m=Powerleveling)&#13;
Written by  and translated by , this guide explains in detail where and how to level up your pets in the most efficient ways possible, from Super-Squirt days all the way to great  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=142</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 11:18:07 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=142</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legendary A.P.E.X.</title>
      <description>&#13;
&#13;
The recent maintenance paved the way for some big changes on Xu-Fuâs Pet Guides. If you joined us on Discord, you will have seen the beginnings of it already. Now itâs time to unveil the big news: Xu-Fu is going to transform from a page dedicated solely to providing the best strategies, to becoming the best pet trading platform on this planet!&#13;
&#13;
We are going to introduce tools for you to compare collections, find compatible trading partners, offer up pets for others and to look for  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=141</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 15:40:20 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=141</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pet Moocher</title>
      <description>Activity has picked up on Xu-Fu and Iâm really excited to introduce you to the latest addition in pet collection tools: The Pet Moocher! Not an April fools joke, itâs a real thing!&#13;
Ever wanted to compare your collection to someone else for any duplicate, cageable pets you can trade between each other? Or maybe just be selfish and see which ones you could mooch from someone else? That doesnât have to be a tedious task with lists and formulas, enter the Pet Moocher! &#13;
&#13;
Sounds like a bad  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=140</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 12:48:10 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=140</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PvP updates with a welcome to Shenk!</title>
      <description>Pet battle PvP has never been my strong suit, making me rely entirely on other people to provide content for this part of the pet battling world. The latest newcomer to the Xu-Fu team kindly offered to provide his knowledge on that, admittedly lacking, part of the page: Welcome to ! &#13;
&#13;
The first new section up is focusing on the achievement Family Brawler (https://www.wow-petguide.com/index.php?m=FamilyBrawler), providing teams for every family right there, but you are of course more than  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=139</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 15:56:54 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=139</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome and thanks Schlumpf!</title>
      <description>Long time no proper announcement, itâs time to change that! And not just because WoW just turned 14 in Europe - Congrats to that!&#13;
&#13;
But there is another thing thatâs overdue to mention:&#13;
For a couple of weeks now, Xu-Fu has seen some immense improvements. Most notably in loading times, which are reduced drastically, but there have been changes in the background in most areas that make the page faster, more flexible and more secure. All of that is thanks to !&#13;
&#13;
Piece by piece he has worked  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=138</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 13:18:26 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=138</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New winner Drawn!</title>
      <description>It turns out that Pantonia already got the little Crackers and was kind enough to pass on, thank you very much for the honesty and friendliness!&#13;
&#13;
That means I was able to draw a new winner from all submissions, aaaaand the lucky one is:&#13;
&#13;
 with his trusty  Captain Snips!&#13;
&#13;
Yarrrr! Congratultions, please check your messages to collect your prize :-)</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=136</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 13:24:49 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=136</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winners announced!</title>
      <description>So many great entries! Way too hard to pick among the cool, cute and piratey pics, so a random roll made the decision for me. And the winners are:&#13;
&#13;
 with Captain Nibs&#13;
 with Brightpaw&#13;
&#13;
Congratulations! &#13;
I will message you here on Xu-Fu, please respond to the message within the next 48 hours (until Wednesday 10/10) or I will have to select a new winner.&#13;
&#13;
And a big thank you to everyone for participating, as well as to Blizzard for sponsoring the codes :-)</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=135</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 09:22:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=135</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cap'n Crackers Giveaway!</title>
      <description>The Giveaway has concluded and no new entries will be accepted! Winners will be announced and contacted shortly. Thank you for participating!&#13;
&#13;
All hands hoay! 'tis time to grab ye some bounty!&#13;
&#13;
Cap'n Crackers be here t' find a new crewmate, 'n it could be ye! Sponsored by Blizzard Europe 'n up fer grabs are two shiny EU loot codes fer this colourful companion. But don't let his appearance fool ye, he's got a nasty beak. Figuratively speakin'.&#13;
&#13;
All ye needs t' be doin' is put on yer finest  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=134</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 13:52:39 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=134</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A few updates!</title>
      <description>Hey :)&#13;
&#13;
Thanks everyone for reaching out about volunteer positions! Still looking, so if you're interested, give me a shout on Discord.&#13;
&#13;
Meanwhile, I have a few news to share around Xu-Fu:&#13;
&#13;
1. A warm (re-) Welcome to the first three volunteers: ,  and !&#13;
&#13;
 will work mostly as News Writer and Content Creator for the German version of the page and I will help develop some better tools to make localized versions of the page easier to navigate.&#13;
 has always been very active in posting advice  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=133</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 14:35:12 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=133</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xu-Fu is looking for volunteers!</title>
      <description>Hello!&#13;
&#13;
With the addition of user-created-strategies, Xu-Fu has entered a new phase and is supporting more and more pet battlers out there in the world. Time to become a bit more structured and organised! &#13;
Volunteers have been a key part of Xu-Fu and I am both proud and grateful for the help I have received. Going forward, I want to make it a better experience for everyone involved, with a clearer role description, better access rights and more decision power for those who help with the  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=132</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 12:54:14 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=132</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New view on your strategies</title>
      <description>When Legion was released, I struggled very hard to keep up with the world quests and test+add strategies. Now with BfA, since everyone can upload strategies, every one of the new quests has a number of different alternatives available already. &#13;
&#13;
It worked out very well, all thanks to you, the creators of all those strategies out there. A BIG THANK YOU!&#13;
&#13;
And as a little treat I've just completed the last important feature for it: A "My Strategies" section!&#13;
Hover over your name on the top  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=131</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 21:36:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=131</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battle for Azeroth</title>
      <description>The release of a new addon is always a very special time. All that anticipation, culminating into the first hours of entering new zones and experiencing all the new content that we only read about or maybe saw some videos. Or played on the beta, but it's not the same right?&#13;
&#13;
All that is going to happen in just one hour. For that, Xu-Fu and I wish you an amazing start into this new expansion. Let everything else be aside for a while, embrace the experience, and enjoy it!</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=130</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 22:58:02 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=130</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add your own Strategies!</title>
      <description>What's that ominous Plus sign right next to each strategy? Your way to add strategies to Xu-Fu of course!&#13;
&#13;
It was long overdue and from this day onward you can stop adding your strategies into comments, because now you have access to a full new toolset allowing you to upload it right there as a new alternative!&#13;
&#13;
Make sure to check out the Strategy Creation Guide if you have questions, or want to know how everything works exactly:  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=129</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 11:27:17 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=129</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battle for Azeroth - Pre-Patch Preparations</title>
      <description>One month to go for Battle for Azeroth, and this week the pre-patch will hit already! With so many changes coming in that patch, a blog entry about it is long overdue.&#13;
&#13;
1. Use your pet charms today!&#13;
Pet Charms as we know it will lose in their value immensely. With the pre-patch comes a new currency and you won't be able to buy upgrading stones with the old charms anymore. So if you still need some or want to stockpile, spend them today!&#13;
Details:  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=128</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 08:43:55 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=128</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Alternatives!</title>
      <description>Another update already!&#13;
This one went much smoother than I expected, and I'm super happy about it. It is feature 2 of 3 core things I need to complete before Battle for Azeroth hits the shelves. That gives me another 6 weeks from now to finish up and have Xu-Fu ready for the next addon. Yay!&#13;
&#13;
Here's what's new today: dynamic alternatives!&#13;
&#13;
The page started out without the possibility to have more than one strategy for a fight. Rather quickly it became necessary to add more, so I created  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=127</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 17:52:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=127</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New section on Xu-Fu unveiled</title>
      <description>Today I am very happy to introduce a new section to Xu-Fuâs Pet Guides. A topic that has been neglected for way too long: Pet PvP!&#13;
&#13;
Rosqo, well known in the pvp world of pet battles, volunteered to work on this section and will fill it with life. He is creating many pet related videos on Youtube to share his team setups and the thoughts behind them. &#13;
Definitely worth checking out! (https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCgC1ZB6nezHiHfvxd4BJrlA)&#13;
&#13;
The first page to go online is an overview of  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=126</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 20:57:35 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=126</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>+100 Intelligence for Xu-Fu!</title>
      <description>First of all, my apologies for the long maintenance! There was a LOT of work that needed to be done for this update and half the page wasnât working during it anyway :D&#13;
&#13;
The Battle Tables desperately needed an overhaul. They are the core part of the page, and yet they were old and dusty. Not any more! It's all fixed, brought up to modern standard, loads much faster and most importantly a ton of new features:&#13;
&#13;
So, whatâs new?&#13;
&#13;
Breeds&#13;
Yes, finally! But what's better than breeds? Stat  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=125</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 21:06:02 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=125</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything at once!</title>
      <description>And then some. Wow, the last weeks flew past like crazy. It's been more than a month since my last blog entry! &#13;
&#13;
Good thing that changes right now :-)&#13;
&#13;
There is a lot happening. Not so much in the pet battling world - Battle for Azeroth is still rather light on pet battling content, I've been told. But in Aranesh's "other" life (besides taking care of little Xu-Fu) things are pretty much in turmoil. And of course, everything happens pretty much at the same time. From a new job in a  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=124</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2018 17:17:46 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=124</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Feature: Intelligent Strategy Creator!</title>
      <description>Xu-Fu is proud to announce a new feature that will come to you very soon: the Fight Organizer - 01, in short: FO-01&#13;
&#13;
An until today unrevealed team of IT scientists working for Xu-Fu has analysed thousands of strategies from pet battlers all over the world and done the impossible: they created FO-01, an artificial intelligence that can create new pet battling strategies better than any human being!&#13;
&#13;
The tool will be available through a simple button as you can see in the screenshot, which  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=123</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2018 11:21:03 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=123</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is that, a new section!?</title>
      <description>Yes, you read that right!&#13;
In the middle of working on the battle tables, I needed a bit of a break and decided to add a different some stuff that makes it easier for all my helpers: An article editor! It's almost done, and I've used it now to add a new little section: My development notes :D&#13;
&#13;
You'll find them by hovering over "News" and selecting, surprise, "Development Notes".&#13;
&#13;
Hope you'll find something interesting in there! :D</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=122</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 16:24:30 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=122</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Development Update</title>
      <description>Today I have a small update on the current development of wow-petguide.com. &#13;
&#13;
Displaying strategies is certainly the key aspect of the page. Yet all new features of the last year were accessories to that. Cool ones, like the collection viewer, but not hitting the core element that brings battlers to visit Xu-Fu on a daily basis.&#13;
&#13;
That is changing with the next update, because I am working on one of the - in my opinion - coolest features for Xu-Fu so far: a complete revamp of the Battle  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=121</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 15:36:57 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=121</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(Un-)Expected downtime</title>
      <description>Yesterday my web space provider performed a scheduled maintenance on wow-petguide.com. Some might have noticed the downtime of a few hours. It was indeed scheduled, but I messed up the times and thought it's next week. &#13;
&#13;
Sorry for the lack of information about it, but luckily it all went fine and the page is back to normal! :-)</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=120</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2018 11:38:30 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=120</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new year, a small update... and Discord!</title>
      <description>Today is the last day of 2017 and oh boy, what a year it has been! So much new content for us pet battlers. We saw the first pet battle dungeons with the Wailing Caverns (https://wow-petguide.com/index.php?m=WailingCritters) and Deadmines (https://wow-petguide.com/index.php?m=Deadmines), dozens of new pets throughout the year, and a whole new set of family challenges with the legendary pets of Argus! &#13;
&#13;
2018 will bring us a new addon and with it surely a brand new set of pet news, and also for  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=119</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 17:59:35 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=119</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy Holidays!</title>
      <description>The Feast of Winter Veil is upon us! &#13;
&#13;
Xu-Fu, Aranesh and the whole team wish you all the best for these festive times and hope you have some wonderful and enchanted days.&#13;
&#13;
</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=118</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2017 17:27:17 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=118</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winter Veil Sale of Pets and Mounts</title>
      <description>If you ever considered one of those shop pets, now might be a good time to revive those thoughts. &#13;
Blizzard activated a large Winter Veil sale that will last until January 3rd with many pets and also mounts reduced by to 50%!&#13;
&#13;
US Offers (https://us.shop.battle.net/en-gb/family/world-of-warcraft)&#13;
EU Offers (https://eu.shop.battle.net/en-gb/family/world-of-warcraft)&#13;
&#13;
Enjoy :-)&#13;
</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=117</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 08:56:58 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=117</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1000 Users! Congratulations to Tovenaar!</title>
      <description>For a short time only - since November - it is possible to register an account with Xu-Fu. And now, less than two months later, a first milestone is reached: please join me in congratulating  for being user number 1000!&#13;
&#13;
It happened much faster than I expected. Actually, I was expecting a lot more problems along the way, but everything seems to work really smoothly :-)&#13;
&#13;
Thanks to everyone for joining and staying with me. It makes me very happy to see this community grow.&#13;
&#13;
And with that  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=116</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 15:11:27 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=116</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pet Ready-Checker - everywhere?</title>
      <description>Sure, why not!&#13;
&#13;
All that work with user accounts and your collection being saved has to lead towards something, doesn't it?&#13;
The first step of that something just went live! &#13;
&#13;
If you go to any of the main categories you will find that the pet table got a big makeover. It loads a lot faster, checks for required pets with much higher accuracy and gives you more info.&#13;
And if you are also logged in with your pet collection saved, you will see that the table automatically checks if you have the  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=115</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 16:47:29 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=115</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xu-Fu goes RSS Feed!</title>
      <description>My last update took a very long time to complete, because most of the features were interlinked with each other. I could not publish any of them without the others being in place. Now that the user system is up and running, I can easily add things on top and also have the time again to work on some smaller, fun things.&#13;
&#13;
For a start, I implemented the suggestion of  to add an RSS feed for the news! &#13;
Since I'm not posting very often, this should give you a convenient way of notification  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=113</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 11:45:13 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=113</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xu-Fu 2.0 is live!</title>
      <description>It's done !!!&#13;
&#13;
I always wanted to add a user account system but in order to do so I had to learn many new things.&#13;
It should be easy to use, with enough features in it, but also well encrypted and secured. All of this took a lot of time, but I'm very proud to announce that Xu-Fu accounts are now live!&#13;
&#13;
Check out the Login button on the top right. I recommend creating an account using your Battle.net account. That way you won't need an additional password and will be logged in  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=112</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 18:11:57 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=112</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aranesh is back :-)</title>
      <description>The last weeks were super relaxing. I saw and learned a lot of new things and spent equally as much time chilling on a beach :D&#13;
Now it's time to put that restored energy to some good use!&#13;
&#13;
But first of all another big thank you for putting together all your insights and ideas for Family Fighter. In those two weeks, more than 3000 comments were submitted! Because of the sheer number of comments, it's the first time I won't manage to read all of them. I'm sorry for any great idea hidden in  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=111</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 11:25:10 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=111</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A big thanks and a small brb</title>
      <description>Argus sure kept us on our toes, but thanks to the many suggestions and comments, all Family Fighter combinations now have strategies!&#13;
Not all of them are perfect, and some amazing ideas are probably still hidden in the sheer mass of suggestions sent in.&#13;
But slowly and steadily, we are going through them and adding more to the page. I want to say a big thank you to , ,  and  in particular, who are actively working on the strategies besides me: your help is truly invaluable!&#13;
&#13;
And of course I  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=110</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2017 08:57:37 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=110</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anomalous onslaught on Argus</title>
      <description>7.3 is a great patch so far with lots to do :-)&#13;
And Xu-Fu is an especially happy little cat right now! Thanks to the immense help of  and  we were able to provide strategies for most of the Anomalous Animals right from patch release! &#13;
&#13;
With the new fights came an incredible increase in activity here. It's absolutely overwhelming and I want to thank you all for trying the fights, sending in suggestions and commenting about your findings. Truth is, there are more comments and suggestions than  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=109</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 11:54:13 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=109</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Argus is almost here!</title>
      <description>Yesterdays announcement at Gamescom in Cologne came as a surprise. Patch 7.3 and with it the new Argus zones is going live next week already, on 29/30th of August!&#13;
&#13;
Well, I can say without a doubt that Illidan was right this time with his favorite quote: Xu-Fu certainly is not fully prepared, yet! &#13;
&#13;
Nevertheless, as of now you can access the pet battle areas for Argus (https://wow-petguide.com/index.php?m=Argus) and of course also for Environeer Bert  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=108</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 12:10:14 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=108</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Say Hi to the Azeroth Adoption Agency</title>
      <description>Today I want to highlight a very special community among the pet battlers: the Azeroth Adoption Agency, or in short A3.&#13;
&#13;
Active mostly in the America region, a whole team of pet collectors around A3s creator Wakamaru (https://twitter.com/TamerWakamaru) are helping pets and players find together for three years already. Since they started in 2014 they have found new homes for more than 6.000 pets!&#13;
&#13;
Taking part is easy enough, no matter if you are looking for pets to adopt, or if youâre a  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=107</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 14:05:03 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=107</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A glimpse of Xu-Fu 2.0</title>
      <description>Today I'm proud to announce a new section on wow-petguide.com: Tools!&#13;
&#13;
Replacing the Home button, this new section will host a growing number of helping hands for anything pet related.&#13;
For the launch there are already two available, which I want to introduce briefly:&#13;
&#13;
Pet Collection Viewer (wow-petguide.com/index.php?m=Collection)&#13;
One of the features coming with Xu-Fu 2.0 is a much better pet import. And while at it, I decided to spend some time in a nicer display of your pet collection.  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=106</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2017 17:51:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=106</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>¡Hola</title>
      <description>I am very pleased to announce the release of the fifth language Xu-Fu is localized to: Spanish!&#13;
&#13;
With more than 400 million native speakers in the world - more than English, it is an immensely welcome addition to the page.&#13;
&#13;
I want to express a big thank you to Darlan for taking on this task and making pet guides even more accessible across the globe.</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=105</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2017 11:30:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=105</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A quick development update</title>
      <description>Wow, time flies! Right before 7.2.5 lands, I want to take the time and give a quick update on the development of Xu-Fu 2.0!&#13;
I hinted towards it last year already (in this news post (https://www.wow-petguide.com/index.php?News=87)), and now I'm slowly reaching the point were things will become real.&#13;
&#13;
This first big release contains many features that all need to be in place together to make sense. &#13;
None of them work without the others, and of course they should work properly and reliable,  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=103</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2017 11:19:20 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=103</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadmines guide live!</title>
      <description>Not much time left until patch 7.2.5 it seems, meaning it is definitely time to prepare for the new pet battle dungeon: The Deadmines!&#13;
&#13;
Xu-Fu's guide section is up now and follows the same pattern as Wailing Critters.&#13;
Check out the required pets and guides here! (https://wow-petguide.com/index.php?m=Deadmines)</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=102</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2017 14:59:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=102</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TD Battle Pet Script</title>
      <description>Today I would like to introduce a small but powerful new addition to Xu-Fu's guides: Scripts for TD BattlePetScript.&#13;
&#13;
A little introduction first: tdBattlePetScript is a fantastic addon created by ldz5 (https://wow.curseforge.com/members/ldz5n) for speeding up PVE pet battles, and removing the element of human error from repetitive battles.&#13;
With it you can create scripts for specific pet battle teams, which will allow you to run the fight by pressing a single hotkey each round. These scripts  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=101</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2017 12:45:19 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=101</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>And the winners are ...</title>
      <description>...selected!&#13;
&#13;
Thank you to everyone who participated, wrote a comment, sent a like or made a compliment. It means a lot! You guys are the best!&#13;
&#13;
The screenshots however, were maybe a little bit too easy ;-)&#13;
The locations in question are indeed the Warsong Hold in Borean Tundra for the Horde:&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
And for the Alliance, it is Lor'danel in Darkshore:&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
Next time, it will be close-ups of smudgy textures :P&#13;
But the most important information is still missing of course, the names of the  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=100</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2017 19:30:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=100</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy Birthday Xu-Fu!</title>
      <description>It's two years already and today we're celebrating Xu-Fu's second anniversary!&#13;
&#13;
In the last year, pet battles saw an immense amount of content, and wow-petguide.com a surge of activity with it! It has been an amazing ride so far and I can only guess what's still to come. And it is all thanks to you! Thank you for visiting, for leaving comments, suggesting improvements, and for simply being an amazing community. I am very happy to be a part of it.&#13;
&#13;
But speaking of giving - in many cultures  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=99</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2017 17:28:08 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=99</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Move of the Falcosaur</title>
      <description>Thanks to the huge effort of , the Falcosaur Team Rumble quests have found their way into Xu-Fu's guides some time ago already.&#13;
&#13;
Now they also found their own, separated space in the form of their own category :-)&#13;
If you are on the Falcosaur quest chain you will ultimetely end up with their individual pet battle quest challenges, and the more than 150 different strategies listed here (https://www.wow-petguide.com/index.php?m=Falcosaur) will hopefully make it a breeze for you!</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=98</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2017 16:55:21 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=98</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wailing Critters and more</title>
      <description>Patch 7.2 is closing in! You can now download it in the background downloader and that means it will most likely arrive within a week or two.&#13;
&#13;
There are many new things coming with this major update patch. I highly recommend checking out a summary from one of the big WoW news pages.&#13;
In terms of pet battles, a good number of new pets are coming, but also new world quest tamers and a whole new pet battle dungeon.&#13;
&#13;
As promised, Xu-Fu got you covered :-)&#13;
Below is an overview and links to the  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=95</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2017 10:39:11 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=95</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wailing Critters Guides</title>
      <description>Hi!&#13;
The Wailing Critters pet battle dungeon is still the biggest pet addition coming in 7.2&#13;
I am preparing my personal guide for the challenge mode, but due to the nature of it I am looking for people interested in providing their own guide.&#13;
&#13;
Why? Well, the pet dungeon is a different kind of challenge. You can't heal or revive pets, okay, but the fights are also not extremely hard like in the Celestial Tournament. There is a huge variety of pets that can beat the individual enemies, but  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=92</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2017 10:53:15 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=92</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch 6.2 Pet Madness!</title>
      <description>The upcoming patch 6.2 will not only introduce the Tanaan Jungle as a new zone, but will also add a huge amount of pet battle opportunities. Currently Draenor does not offer many dailies and this patch appears to address this.&#13;
&#13;
Similar to the Beasts of Fable, you will face legendary pets spread throughout the Tanaan Jungle. Luckily you won't have to chase them down since they will stay in place, like the legendary beasts in Pandaria.&#13;
&#13;
However they will pose a different challenge in that  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=11</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 10:36:12 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=11</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Feature incoming!</title>
      <description>The Darkmoon Faire is over already and new challenges await!&#13;
To me work on the page never stops and I'm delighted to see it kicking off so well.&#13;
By now Xu-Fu sees about 150 visitors every day from all over the world. Thanks for stopping by and a special thanks to everyone who is leaving a comment or suggesting new features.&#13;
&#13;
Oh yeah, what is that about new features!?&#13;
I'm currently working on one and it's almost done: alternative strategies!&#13;
&#13;
Once everything is ready you will see tabs  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=10</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2015 20:43:53 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=10</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Darkmoon Faire!</title>
      <description>The Darkmoon Faire is among us again! This month you can earn even more achievements with the new racer, or should I rather say "flier" ^^&#13;
&#13;
In terms of pet battles nothing has changed, you will still find the two usual dailies available. &#13;
I posted strategies that you can use to also level pets up and that don't use any exotic or rare pets. &#13;
&#13;
Hope you have a good time!</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=9</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2015 16:27:53 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=9</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let the guide begin!</title>
      <description>Welcome to Xu-Fu's Pet Battle Guides!&#13;
&#13;
Today marks the start of this little project.&#13;
&#13;
For a long time I have been doing my daily battles, leveling my pets and trying myself on new challenges. I tried different ways to memorize all the strategies I use. But with more and more fights, nothing felt convenient enough in quickly providing access to the information I needed: what pets, what spells and what rotation to use.&#13;
&#13;
And thus the first version of my own pet guides started, as an online  [...]</description>
      <link>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=5</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 12:04:10 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wow-petguide.com/?News=5</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
